Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/earlyindrya (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

User Interface Design
User Experience Design (UED)
Graphic Design

Certifications

Complete UI Designer: Visual Design, Prototype, Usability Testing UI/UX Design Mastery UX Academy UI/UX Design Ekskul UI/UX

Honors-Awards

Best UI Design Short-Bootcamp Peduli Digital

Early Indrya Pramesti

UI Designer Intern at Campaign.com | GDSC UG Core Team Media Creative

Depok

Summary

A UI Designer Intern with 2+ years of experience in UI/UX Design. I have experience working as part of the team and individually with high-level skills in Figma. In two years, I finished several projects which created useful products and specialized in creating UI Design.

Specialties: Mobile App Design, Web Design, Graphic Design, and Illustration

Also check my works at dribbble.com/earlyindrya

Experience

Campaign.com
UI Designer
February 2022 - Present (4 months)

Just Design Indonesia Web Designer February 2022 - Present (4 months)

GDSC Universitas Gunadarma

9 months

Core Team Media Creative September 2021 - Present (9 months)

Google Developers is a program for university students. Designed to help them build their skills and knowledge regarding mobile, web, and machine learning development. DSC is intended to be a space where students, developers, and teachers can get their place to share their insights and make positive influence to the people around them.

 Created appealing design used in social media promotional materials for community • Designed social media needs for Instagram, banners, and certificates.

Member Community
September 2021 - Present (9 months)

BuildWith Angga UI Designer December 2021 - March 2022 (4 months) Indonesia

BuildWith Angga is an online classes to learn design, code, business in building website/mobile applications that are useful for the community.

Xportee Indonesia
Product Designer
August 2021 - November 2021 (4 months)

Xportee is the first end-to-end solution that connects MSMEs with investors and mentors to help MSMEs #NaikKelas with export activities.

- Worked with Product Analyst on User Reaserch and ideating solution based on interview results.
- Designed a mobile and web interfaces, including sketching, wireframing, and usability testing.

Kampus Indonesia - PT Inspirasi Mandiri Nusantara Graphic Designer April 2021 - August 2021 (5 months) Malang, East Java, Indonesia

Kampus Indonesia is an updated information media platform about higher education information, campuses, scholarships, internships and self-development training as well as tools in student interests and talents.

- Created several design options for each social media developed from the Standard Manuals Graph (GSM).
- Make a content design that has been curated according to the amount of content on the timetine.

Comma Design
7 months

Media Team
December 2020 - April 2021 (5 months)

Comma Design is an acronym for "Community Mahasiswa Design" Comma Design Community Students. Comma Design is Gunadarma University Student Organization who has learning and teaching activities in Graphic Design.

- Members of The Governing Body As MOC (Media of Communication)
 Divison
- Members of Media Design Division: Creating Instagram Feeds Design template.

Member Community
October 2020 - December 2020 (3 months)

Education

University of Gunadarma

Undergraduate Information System Student · (December 2019 - December 2023)